[{"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985410", "answer": "arbeiten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "arbeitete", "chunk": 0, "info2": "gearbeitet", "question": "\uc77c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985449", "answer": "begr\u00fc\u00dfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "begr\u00fc\u00dfte", "chunk": 0, "info2": "begr\u00fc\u00dft", "question": "\uc778\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985461", "answer": "hei\u00dfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "hie\u00df", "chunk": 0, "info2": "gehei\u00dfen", "question": "\ubd88\ub9ac\uc6b0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985471", "answer": "kommen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "kam", "chunk": 0, "info2": "gekommen", "question": "\uc624\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985480", "answer": "korrigieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "korrigierte", "chunk": 0, "info2": "korrigiert", "question": "\uace0\uce58\ub2e4 \ucca8\uc0ad\ud558\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985490", "answer": "malen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "malte", "chunk": 0, "info2": "gemalt", "question": "\uadf8\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985500", "answer": "passen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "passte", "chunk": 1, "info2": "gepasst", "question": "\uc5b4\uc6b8\ub9ac\ub2e4 \uc54c\ub9de\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985509", "answer": "sammeln", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sammelte", "chunk": 1, "info2": "gesammelt", "question": "\ubaa8\uc73c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985518", "answer": "sein", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "war", "chunk": 1, "info2": "gewesen", "question": "~\uc774\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985527", "answer": "tauschen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "tauschte", "chunk": 1, "info2": "getauscht", "question": "\uad50\ud658\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985536", "answer": "vorstellen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "stellte...vor", "chunk": 1, "info2": "vorgestellt", "question": "\uc18c\uac1c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985544", "answer": "beginnen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "begann", "chunk": 1, "info2": "begonnen", "question": "\uc2dc\uc791\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985553", "answer": "besuchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "besuchte", "chunk": 2, "info2": "besucht", "question": "\ubc29\ubb38\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985561", "answer": "brauchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "brauchte", "chunk": 2, "info2": "gebraucht", "question": "\ud558\ub2e4 \ud544\uc694\ub85c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985571", "answer": "finden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "fand", "chunk": 2, "info2": "gefunden", "question": "\uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4 \ucc3e\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985580", "answer": "funktionieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "funktionierte", "chunk": 2, "info2": "funktioniert", "question": "\uc791\ub3d9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985589", "answer": "geben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "gab", "chunk": 2, "info2": "gegeben", "question": "\uc8fc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985598", "answer": "erg\u00e4nzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "erg\u00e4nzte", "chunk": 2, "info2": "erg\u00e4nzt", "question": "\ub123\ub2e4 \ucc44\uc6cc", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985608", "answer": "gefallen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "gefiel", "chunk": 3, "info2": "gefallen", "question": "\ub4e4\ub2e4 \ub9c8\uc74c\uc5d0 ~\uc758", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985617", "answer": "gehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "ging", "chunk": 3, "info2": "gegangen", "question": "\uac00\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985637", "answer": "gr\u00fcnden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "gr\u00fcndete", "chunk": 3, "info2": "gegr\u00fcndet", "question": "\ud558\ub2e4 \uae30\ucd08\ub85c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985654", "answer": "gr\u00fc\u00dfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "gr\u00fc\u00dfte", "chunk": 3, "info2": "gegr\u00fc\u00dft", "question": "\uc804\ud558\ub2e4 \uc548\ubd80\ub97c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985672", "answer": "haben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "hatte", "chunk": 3, "info2": "gehabt", "question": "\uac00\uc9c0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985681", "answer": "kennen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "kannte", "chunk": 3, "info2": "gekannt", "question": "\uc54c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985690", "answer": "lernen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "lernte", "chunk": 4, "info2": "gelernt", "question": "\ubc30\uc6b0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985699", "answer": "machen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "machte", "chunk": 4, "info2": "gemacht", "question": "\ub9cc\ub4e4\ub2e4 \ud558\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985709", "answer": "planen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "plante", "chunk": 4, "info2": "geplant", "question": "\uacc4\ud68d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985717", "answer": "tanzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "tanzte", "chunk": 4, "info2": "getanzt", "question": "\ucda4\ucd94\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985726", "answer": "lesen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "las", "chunk": 4, "info2": "gelesen", "question": "\uc77d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985734", "answer": "telefonieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "telefonierte", "chunk": 4, "info2": "telefoniert", "question": "\uac78\ub2e4 \uc804\ud654\ub97c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985744", "answer": "zeigen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "zeigte", "chunk": 5, "info2": "gezeigt", "question": "\ubcf4\uc5ec\uc8fc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985752", "answer": "essen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "a\u00df", "chunk": 5, "info2": "gegessen", "question": "\uba39\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985763", "answer": "trinken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "trank", "chunk": 5, "info2": "getrunken", "question": "\ub9c8\uc2dc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985772", "answer": "besprechen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "besprach", "chunk": 5, "info2": "besprochen", "question": "\ud611\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985781", "answer": "erz\u00e4hlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "erz\u00e4hlte", "chunk": 5, "info2": "erz\u00e4hlt", "question": "\uc774\uc57c\uae30\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985790", "answer": "kosten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "kostete", "chunk": 5, "info2": "gekostet", "question": "\ub4e4\ub2e4 \ube44\uc6a9\uc774", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985799", "answer": "tun", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "tat", "chunk": 6, "info2": "getan", "question": "\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985808", "answer": "vergleichen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "verglich", "chunk": 6, "info2": "verglichen", "question": "\ube44\uad50\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985816", "answer": "bekommen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "bekam", "chunk": 6, "info2": "bekommen", "question": "\ubc1b\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985824", "answer": "bezahlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "bezahlte", "chunk": 6, "info2": "bezahlt", "question": "\uc9c0\ubd88\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985833", "answer": "erlauben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "erlaubte", "chunk": 6, "info2": "erlaubt", "question": "\ud5c8\ub77d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985844", "answer": "fahren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "fuhr", "chunk": 6, "info2": "gefahren", "question": "\uac00\ub2e4 \ud0c0\uace0", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985853", "answer": "feiern", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "feierte", "chunk": 7, "info2": "gefeiert", "question": "\uae30\ub150\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985862", "answer": "tragen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "trug", "chunk": 7, "info2": "getragen", "question": "\uc6b4\ubc18\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985870", "answer": "klingeln", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "klingelte", "chunk": 7, "info2": "geklingelt", "question": "\uc6b8\ub9ac\ub2e4 \ubca8\uc774", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985879", "answer": "ankommen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "kam\u2026an", "chunk": 7, "info2": "angekommen", "question": "\ub3c4\ucc29\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985888", "answer": "bewundern", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "bewunderte", "chunk": 7, "info2": "bewundert", "question": "\uacbd\ud0c4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985897", "answer": "organisieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "organisierte", "chunk": 7, "info2": "organisiert", "question": "\ud615\uc131\ud558\ub2e4 \uc870\uc9c1\ud558\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985906", "answer": "passieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "passierte", "chunk": 8, "info2": "passiert", "question": "\ubc1c\uc0dd\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985915", "answer": "putzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "putzte", "chunk": 8, "info2": "geputzt", "question": "\uccad\uc18c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985926", "answer": "schaffen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "schuf", "chunk": 8, "info2": "geschaffen", "question": "\ucc3d\uc870\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985934", "answer": "schlafen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "schlief", "chunk": 8, "info2": "geschlafen", "question": "\uc790\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985943", "answer": "schauen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "schaute", "chunk": 8, "info2": "geschaut", "question": "\ubc14\ub77c\ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985951", "answer": "sehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sah", "chunk": 8, "info2": "gesehen", "question": "\ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985960", "answer": "st\u00fcrzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "st\u00fcrzte", "chunk": 9, "info2": "gest\u00fcrzt", "question": "\ucd94\ub77d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985969", "answer": "suchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "suchte", "chunk": 9, "info2": "gesucht", "question": "\ucc3e\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985977", "answer": "treffen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "traf", "chunk": 9, "info2": "getroffen", "question": "\ub9cc\ub098\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985986", "answer": "wissen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "wusste", "chunk": 9, "info2": "gewusst", "question": "\uc54c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.985995", "answer": "w\u00fcnschen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "w\u00fcnschte", "chunk": 9, "info2": "gew\u00fcnscht", "question": "\ubc14\ub77c\ub2e4 \uc6d0\ud558\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986004", "answer": "abholen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "holte...ab", "chunk": 9, "info2": "abgeholt", "question": "\uac00\ub2e4 \ub370\ub9ac\ub7ec", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986015", "answer": "aufmachen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "machte...auf", "chunk": 10, "info2": "aufgemacht", "question": "\uc5f4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986024", "answer": "ausgehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "ging...aus", "chunk": 10, "info2": "ausgegangen", "question": "\uc548\ub418\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986033", "answer": "schneiden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "schnitt", "chunk": 10, "info2": "geschnitten", "question": "\uc790\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986041", "answer": "anrufen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "rief...an", "chunk": 10, "info2": "angerufen", "question": "\ud1b5\ud654\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986050", "answer": "antworten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "antwortete", "chunk": 10, "info2": "geantwortet", "question": "\ub300\ub2f5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986058", "answer": "anschauen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "schaute...an", "chunk": 10, "info2": "angeschaut", "question": "\uc751\uc2dc\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986067", "answer": "singen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sang", "chunk": 11, "info2": "gesungen", "question": "\ub178\ub798\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986075", "answer": "aussehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sah...aus", "chunk": 11, "info2": "ausgesehen", "question": "\ubcf4\uc774\ub2e4 ~\ub85c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986084", "answer": "benutzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "benutzte", "chunk": 11, "info2": "benutzt", "question": "\uc0ac\uc6a9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986093", "answer": "beschreiben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "beschrieb", "chunk": 11, "info2": "beschrieben", "question": "\ubb18\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986108", "answer": "bleiben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "blieb", "chunk": 11, "info2": "geblieben", "question": "\uba38\ubb34\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986118", "answer": "dauern", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "dauerte", "chunk": 11, "info2": "gedauert", "question": "\uac78\ub9ac\ub2e4 \uc2dc\uac04\uc774", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986127", "answer": "denken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "dachte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "gedacht", "question": "\uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986136", "answer": "duschen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "duschte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "geduscht", "question": "\uc0e4\uc6cc\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986144", "answer": "erreichen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "erreichte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "erreicht", "question": "\ub3c4\ub2ec\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986153", "answer": "glauben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "glaubte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "geglaubt", "question": "\uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4 \ubbff\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986162", "answer": "informieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "informierte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "informiert", "question": "\uc8fc\ub2e4 \uc815\ubcf4\ub97c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986171", "answer": "mitbringen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "brachte\u2026mit", "chunk": 12, "info2": "mitgebracht", "question": "\uc624\ub2e4 \ub370\ub9ac\uace0", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986180", "answer": "abfahren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "fuhr\u2026ab", "chunk": 13, "info2": "abgefahren", "question": "\ucd9c\ubc1c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986190", "answer": "bestellen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "bestellte", "chunk": 13, "info2": "bestellt", "question": "\uc8fc\ubb38\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986201", "answer": "reden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "redete", "chunk": 13, "info2": "geredet", "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986210", "answer": "regnen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "regnete", "chunk": 13, "info2": "geregnet", "question": "\uc624\ub2e4 \ube44\uac00", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986219", "answer": "reparieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "reparierte", "chunk": 13, "info2": "repariert", "question": "\uc218\ub9ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986227", "answer": "sitzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sa\u00df", "chunk": 13, "info2": "gesessen", "question": "\uc788\ub2e4 \uc549\uc544", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986237", "answer": "stehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "stand", "chunk": 14, "info2": "gestanden", "question": "\uc788\ub2e4 \uc11c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986246", "answer": "messen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "ma\u00df", "chunk": 14, "info2": "gemessen", "question": "\uce21\uc815\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986254", "answer": "verbringen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "verbrachte", "chunk": 14, "info2": "verbracht", "question": "\ubcf4\ub0b4\ub2e4 \uc2dc\uac04\uc744", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986265", "answer": "vergessen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "verga\u00df", "chunk": 14, "info2": "vergessen", "question": "\uc78a\uc5b4\ubc84\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986276", "answer": "verwenden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "verwendete", "chunk": 14, "info2": "verwendet", "question": "\uc0ac\uc6a9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986285", "answer": "wechseln", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "wechselte", "chunk": 14, "info2": "gewechselt", "question": "\uad50\uccb4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986294", "answer": "fehlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "fehlte", "chunk": 15, "info2": "gefehlt", "question": "\ubd80\uc871\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986303", "answer": "anfangen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "fing...an", "chunk": 15, "info2": "angefangen", "question": "\uc2dc\uc791\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986311", "answer": "anprobieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "probierte...an", "chunk": 15, "info2": "anprobiert", "question": "\uc785\uc5b4\ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986324", "answer": "ansto\u00dfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sto\u00dfte...an", "chunk": 15, "info2": "angesto\u00dft", "question": "\uac74\ubc30\ud558\ub2e4 \ubc00\uce58\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986336", "answer": "aufpassen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "passte\u2026auf", "chunk": 15, "info2": "aufgepasst", "question": "\uc8fc\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986345", "answer": "ausf\u00fchren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "f\u00fchrte...aus", "chunk": 15, "info2": "ausgef\u00fchrt", "question": "\uc218\ucd9c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986353", "answer": "bedeuten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "bedeutete", "chunk": 16, "info2": "bedeutet", "question": "\uc758\ubbf8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986362", "answer": "bringen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "brachte", "chunk": 16, "info2": "gebracht", "question": "\uc624\ub2e4 \uac00\uc9c0\uace0", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986372", "answer": "kaufen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "kaufte", "chunk": 16, "info2": "gekauft", "question": "\uad6c\ub9e4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986381", "answer": "eingeben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "gab...ein", "chunk": 16, "info2": "eingegeben", "question": "\ubcf5\uc6a9\uc2dc\ud0a4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986390", "answer": "einladen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "lud...ein", "chunk": 16, "info2": "eingeladen", "question": "\ucd08\ub300\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986398", "answer": "entschuldigen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "entschuldigte", "chunk": 16, "info2": "entschuldigt", "question": "\uc6a9\uc11c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986406", "answer": "erkl\u00e4ren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "erkl\u00e4rte", "chunk": 17, "info2": "erkl\u00e4rt", "question": "\uc124\uba85\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986415", "answer": "fernsehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sah...fern", "chunk": 17, "info2": "ferngesehen", "question": "\ubcf4\ub2e4 TV\ub97c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986424", "answer": "festhalten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "hielt\u2026fest", "chunk": 17, "info2": "festgehalten", "question": "\uace0\uc9d1\ud558\ub2e4 \ubd99\uc7a1\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986433", "answer": "helfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "half", "chunk": 17, "info2": "geholfen", "question": "\ub3d5\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986445", "answer": "holen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "holte", "chunk": 17, "info2": "geholt", "question": "\uaebc\ub0b4\ub2e4 \uac00\uc838\uc624\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986454", "answer": "kopieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "kopierte", "chunk": 17, "info2": "kopiert", "question": "\ubcf5\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986465", "answer": "l\u00e4cheln", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "l\u00e4chelte", "chunk": 18, "info2": "gel\u00e4chelt", "question": "\uc9d3\ub2e4 \ubbf8\uc18c\ub97c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986474", "answer": "mailen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "mailte", "chunk": 18, "info2": "gemailt", "question": "\ubcf4\ub0b4\ub2e4 \uba54\uc77c\uc744", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986483", "answer": "nachfragen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "fragte\u2026nach", "chunk": 18, "info2": "nachgefragt", "question": "\ubb38\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986491", "answer": "nehmen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "nahm", "chunk": 18, "info2": "genommen", "question": "\uac00\uc9c0\ub2e4 \ucde8\ud558\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986500", "answer": "nennen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "nannte", "chunk": 18, "info2": "genannt", "question": "\uba85\uba85\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986509", "answer": "sagen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sagte", "chunk": 18, "info2": "gesagt", "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986517", "answer": "empfehlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "empfahl", "chunk": 19, "info2": "empfohlen", "question": "\ucd94\ucc9c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986528", "answer": "fliegen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "flog", "chunk": 19, "info2": "geflogen", "question": "\ub0a0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986536", "answer": "tr\u00e4umen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "t\u00e4umte", "chunk": 19, "info2": "getr\u00e4umt", "question": "\uafc8\uafb8\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986545", "answer": "vermuten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "vermutete", "chunk": 19, "info2": "vermutet", "question": "\ucd94\uce21\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986555", "answer": "versuchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "versuchte", "chunk": 19, "info2": "versucht", "question": "\uc2dc\ub3c4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986564", "answer": "warten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "wartete", "chunk": 19, "info2": "gewartet", "question": "\uae30\ub2e4\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986573", "answer": "beenden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "beendete", "chunk": 20, "info2": "beendet", "question": "\ub05d\ub0b4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986581", "answer": "laufen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "lief", "chunk": 20, "info2": "gelaufen", "question": "\ub2ec\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986592", "answer": "danken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "dankte", "chunk": 20, "info2": "gedankt", "question": "\uac10\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986604", "answer": "lassen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "lie\u00df", "chunk": 20, "info2": "gelassen", "question": "\ud558\ub2e4 \ud558\uac8c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986613", "answer": "aufr\u00e4umen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "r\u00e4umte...auf", "chunk": 20, "info2": "aufger\u00e4umt", "question": "\uc815\ub9ac\uc815\ub3c8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986621", "answer": "h\u00f6ren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "h\u00f6rte", "chunk": 20, "info2": "geh\u00f6rt", "question": "\ub4e3\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986632", "answer": "treiben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "trieb", "chunk": 21, "info2": "getrieben", "question": "\ubab0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986641", "answer": "heiraten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "heiratete", "chunk": 21, "info2": "geheiratet", "question": "\uacb0\ud63c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986650", "answer": "lachen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "lachte", "chunk": 21, "info2": "gelacht", "question": "\uc6c3\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986658", "answer": "leben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "lebte", "chunk": 21, "info2": "gelebt", "question": "\uc0b4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986667", "answer": "reisen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "reiste", "chunk": 21, "info2": "gereist", "question": "\uc5ec\ud589\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986675", "answer": "schmecken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "schmeckte", "chunk": 21, "info2": "geschmeckt", "question": "\ub098\ub2e4 \ub9db\uc774", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986684", "answer": "sterben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "starb", "chunk": 22, "info2": "gestorben", "question": "\uc8fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986693", "answer": "studieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "studierte", "chunk": 22, "info2": "studiert", "question": "\uc804\uacf5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986704", "answer": "verstehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "verstand", "chunk": 22, "info2": "verstanden", "question": "\uc774\ud574\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986714", "answer": "schwimmen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "schwamm", "chunk": 22, "info2": "geschwommen", "question": "\uc218\uc601\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986725", "answer": "unterrichten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "unterrichtete", "chunk": 22, "info2": "unterrichtet", "question": "\ud558\ub2e4 \uc218\uc5c5\uc744", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986734", "answer": "werden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "wurde", "chunk": 22, "info2": "geworden", "question": "\ub418\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986743", "answer": "gewinnen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "gewann", "chunk": 23, "info2": "gewonnen", "question": "\uc5bb\ub2e4 \uc774\uae30\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986752", "answer": "lieben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "liebte", "chunk": 23, "info2": "geliebt", "question": "\uc0ac\ub791\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986760", "answer": "stehlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "stahl", "chunk": 23, "info2": "gestohlen", "question": "\ud6d4\uce58\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986768", "answer": "probieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "probierte", "chunk": 23, "info2": "probiert", "question": "\ud574\ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986777", "answer": "zahlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "zahlte", "chunk": 23, "info2": "gezahlt", "question": "\uce58\ub974\ub2e4 \uac12\uc744", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986785", "answer": "dekorieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "dekorierte", "chunk": 23, "info2": "dekoriert", "question": "\uc7a5\uc2dd\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986794", "answer": "schenken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "schenkte", "chunk": 24, "info2": "geschenkt", "question": "\uc120\ubb3c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986802", "answer": "brechen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "brach", "chunk": 24, "info2": "gebrochen", "question": "\ubd80\ub7ec\uc9c0\ub2e4 \uae68\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986814", "answer": "buchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "buchte", "chunk": 24, "info2": "gebucht", "question": "\uc608\uc57d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986822", "answer": "l\u00fcgen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "log", "chunk": 24, "info2": "gelogen", "question": "\uac70\uc9d3\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986831", "answer": "sprechen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "sprach", "chunk": 24, "info2": "gesprochen", "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986840", "answer": "h\u00e4ngen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "hing", "chunk": 24, "info2": "gehangen", "question": "\uac78\ub824\uc788\ub2e4 \uac78\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986851", "answer": "liegen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "lag", "chunk": 25, "info2": "gelegen", "question": "\ub193\ub2e4 \ub215\ud788\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986860", "answer": "legen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "legte", "chunk": 25, "info2": "gelegt", "question": "\ub193\uc5ec\uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986869", "answer": "spielen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "spielte", "chunk": 25, "info2": "gespielt", "question": "\ub180\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986878", "answer": "stellen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "stellte", "chunk": 25, "info2": "gestellt", "question": "\uc138\uc6cc\ub450\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986886", "answer": "bestehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "bestand", "chunk": 25, "info2": "bestanden", "question": "\ud569\uaca9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986898", "answer": "kochen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "kochte", "chunk": 25, "info2": "gekocht", "question": "\uc694\ub9ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986907", "answer": "teilen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "teilte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "geteilt", "question": "\ub098\ub204\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986916", "answer": "waschen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "wusch", "chunk": 26, "info2": "gewaschen", "question": "\uc53b\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986924", "answer": "brennen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "brannte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "gebrannt", "question": "\ud0c0\ub2e4 \ubd88\uc5d0", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986935", "answer": "wandern", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "wanderte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "gewandert", "question": "\uac77\ub2e4 \ub4f1\ubc18\ud558\ub2e4,", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986944", "answer": "\u00fcbersetzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "\u00fcbersetzte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "\u00fcbersetzt", "question": "\ubc88\uc5ed\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986953", "answer": "rauchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "rauchte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "geraucht", "question": "\ud53c\ub2e4 \ub2f4\ubc30\ub97c", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986962", "answer": "verschieben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "verschob", "chunk": 27, "info2": "verschoben", "question": "\uc5f0\uae30\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986971", "answer": "verbinden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "verband", "chunk": 27, "info2": "verbunden", "question": "\uc5f0\uacb0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.986988", "answer": "retten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "rettete", "chunk": 27, "info2": "gerettet", "question": "\uad6c\ucd9c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-23 23:16:48.987014", "answer": "spazieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "spazierte", "chunk": 27, "info2": "spaziert", "question": "\uc0b0\ucc45\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}]